Julian P

Web Developer Student

Gloucester iulian.prodea@gmail.com +447424693338

Hey reader, I am Iulian or Julian if it's more easy for you. I am born in Romania but for more than half a year I am a resident in the UK, with the right to stay, currently for 5 years. Before coming to the UK, I worked in my country, gaining extensive experience mainly in dealing with clients, especially working in the insurance industry. I started from a beginner position and I evolved, step by step, to midle management and even top management positions. Now, I decided to reinvent myself. The IT field, and especially the software programming, have always attracted me, I can say that it was and still is like a hobby for me. Currently I am based in Gloucester, Gloucestershire, UK but I am ready for relocation.

I decided to take my passion to a professional level, which is why I moved to the UK and started studying the online course provided by Code Institute Ireland at the end of which I will graduate with a Level 5 Diploma, Full Stack Software Development. During this course I studied HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, API's, and I will study until May 2020, Python, Django, Flask, MongoDB, MySQL. How has the journey been so far? Amazing. I learned a lot of interesting and exciting things and I can't wait to see how the back-end side is.

Where do I want to go? I want to become the expert as I was in insurance industry but this time in coding. And that's because the attention to details, the desire to always be in control of myself and my professional abilities and skills, made me adept at always doing things well.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Support Worker

Holmleigh Care Homes Ltd, Gloucester UK August 2019 to Present

- Facilitating socialisation and social activities e.g. visiting family/friends, walks, cinema/theatre, meals out.
- Monitoring progress and recording notes on daily record sheets relating to each visit.
- Liaise with families, friends, advocates, external agencies and the management team to provide a consistent approach that meets the individual needs of each service user.
- Empathise and actively listen in a sensitive manner accessing appropriate additional support where necessary.
- Support Service Users to access appropriate health care provision enabling them to make an informed choice regarding any prescribed treatment, seeking advice where necessary.
- Create opportunities for Service Users to develop establish and maintain personal relationships and social networks, which encourage greater participation and integration in their chosen communities.
- Preparing and participating in group and/or one-to-one therapy sessions, both individually and with other health professionals.

Area Manager, in Insurances

City Insurance - Cluj Napoca, Romania October 2015 to August 2019

- Strategic planning
- Managing projects
- Giving presentations
- Providing customer service / support
- Writing reports
- Leading a team

Branch Manager, in Insurances

City Insurance - Bucharest, Romania October 2014 to October 2015

- Strategic planning
- Managing projects
- Giving presentations
- Providing customer service / support
- · Writing reports
- · Leading a team

Insurance Advisor, in Insurances

City Insurance - Bucharest, Romania April 2012 to October 2014

- · Writing reports
- Giving presentations
- Managing projects
- · Working with data
- Sales
- Providing customer service / support
- Account management

Education

Diploma of Higher Education in Computer Science, FuulStack Software Development (currently studying)

Code Institute Ireland

November 2019 to May 2020

Skills

HTML5 (Less than 1 year), Javascript (Less than 1 year), jQuery (Less than 1 year), Bootstrap 4 (Less than 1 year), CSS3 (Less than 1 year), GitHub (Less than 1 year), JSON (Less than 1 year), Google Maps API's (Less than 1 year), VS Code (Less than 1 year), Version Control Git (Less than 1 year)

Links

https://github.com/iulianpro?tab=stars

https://www.coderlist.io/profile/iulianpro